[Music]
he was begging for my endorsement I
could have said mitt drop to your knees
he would have dropped to his knees he
was begging what do you think he really
meant break it down for us he means that
Romney would suck as man name a minority
that hasn't been screwed over by this
country if we pay everyone we'll be like
$19 trillion in debts we already are
well that's exactly why we can't afford
it look the US $20,000 to every living
victim of World War II Japanese
internment camps yeah but that cost like
$1.2 billion and that's what one and a
half stealth bombers I think we have the
money a few years back I was casted to
play older de bastard from wuang right
and um it's been a few years we trying
to know move this rock up the hill but
you know I am now a man of a certain age
and we all know that you know Rusty died
in his young 30s you know there's going
to come a point where I'm not going to
feel comfortable playing that role any
I'm I'm I'm old ass
man